<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>UglyFeed</title>
    <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com</link>
    <description>The ugliest, funniest news you'll ever read!</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>

    <item>
      <title>Man Sues Himself and Wins! Judge's Head Explodes!</title>
      <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com/man-sues-himself</link>
      <description>A local man sued himself for emotional distress and won, leaving the judge in utter disbelief and the audience in stitches.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>1</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Cat Becomes Mayor, Declares Naptime for All</title>
      <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com/cat-mayor</link>
      <description>A cat named Whiskers has been elected mayor, implementing a mandatory naptime policy that has the town in a frenzy of relaxation.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>2</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Invisible Art Exhibit Draws Huge Crowds</title>
      <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com/invisible-art</link>
      <description>An art exhibit featuring invisible paintings has attracted massive crowds, with visitors marveling at the emperor's new clothes of the art world.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 09:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>3</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Helicopter Delivers World's Largest Pizza, Causes Chaos</title>
      <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com/helicopter-pizza</link>
      <description>A pizzeria delivered the world's largest pizza by helicopter, causing a feeding frenzy and traffic chaos in the city.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>4</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Robot Announces Presidential Run, Promises to Fix Everything</title>
      <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com/robot-president</link>
      <description>A robot named RoboBob has declared its candidacy for president, promising to eliminate inefficiencies and bring a new era of automation.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 08:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>5</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Alien Abduction Insurance Claims on the Rise</title>
      <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com/alien-insurance</link>
      <description>Claims for alien abduction insurance have increased dramatically, with more people reporting close encounters of the absurd kind.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>6</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Man Sets Record for Longest Burp, Neighbors Complain</title>
      <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com/longest-burp</link>
      <description>A man has broken the world record for the longest burp, much to the annoyance of his neighbors who endured the 2-minute spectacle.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 06:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>7</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Giant Rubber Duck Transport Causes Citywide Traffic Snarl</title>
      <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com/rubber-duck-traffic</link>
      <description>A giant rubber duck being transported through the city caused a massive traffic jam, providing endless amusement for pedestrians.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>8</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Banana Peel Slips Lead to Ban on Bananas</title>
      <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com/banana-ban</link>
      <description>A city has banned bananas after a series of comical but dangerous banana peel slips raised public safety concerns.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 05:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>9</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Man Weds Refrigerator in Frosty Ceremony</title>
      <link>http://www.uglyfeed.com/refrigerator-marriage</link>
      <description>A man has married his refrigerator in a bizarre ceremony, declaring it the coolest relationship he's ever had.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 04:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>10</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
